nozhit.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Nozhit.com uses and protects any information that you give Nozhit.com when you use this website. Nozhit.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Nozhit.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

Cookies

This website uses tracking software to monitor it's visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website but will not store, save or collect personal information. Some of our quizzes also use cookies to save your progress and results. Let us say we have a game where you can open a hatch each day in a christmas calendar. We will use cookies to store information about which hatches are opened. We will not use these cookies in any other way. 

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
